[
    {
        "queryProperty" : "type",
        "question": "What meal type are you looking for?",
        "response": ["breakfast", "lunch/dinner", "dessert", "other"]
    },
    {
        "queryProperty" : "type",
        "question": "if other",
        "response": ["snack", "soup", "bread", "salad", "drink"]
    },
    {
        "queryProperty" : "maxReadyTime",
      "question": "maxReadyTime?",
      "response": ["15", "30", "60", "limitless"]
    },
    {
        "queryProperty" : "equipment",
        "question": "equipments you dont have",
        "response": ["oven", "food processor", "blender", "crockpot"]
    },
    {
    "queryProperty" : "cuisine",
      "question": "cuisine",
      "response": ["american", "european", "asian", "south american", "other"]
    },
    {
        "queryProperty" : "cuisine",
        "question": "american",
        "response": ["american", "Southern", "Cajun"]
    },
    {
        "queryProperty" : "cuisine",
        "question": "european",
        "response": ["british", "italian", "french", "german", "greek"]
    },
    {
        "queryProperty" : "cuisine",
        "question": "asian",
        "response": ["chinese", "korean", "japanese", "thai", "viet", "indian"]
    },
    {
        "queryProperty" : "cuisine",
        "question": "south american",
        "response": ["mexican", "Latin American", "Caribbean"]
    },
    {
        "queryProperty" : "cuisine",
        "question": "other",
        "response": ["Jewish", "African", "Mediterranean"]
    },
    {
        "queryProperty" : "intolerances",
      "question": "intolerances",
      "response": ["peanut", "gulten", "dairy", "seafood", "soy"]
    },
    {
        "queryProperty" : "diet",
      "question": "diet",
      "response": ["Vegetarian", "Vegan", "Ketogenic", "Pescetarian"]
    },
    {
        "queryProperty" : "maxCalories",
      "question": "maxCalories",
      "response": ["200", "500", "limitless"]
    }
]